ugblizz.com 2015-09-19

# Blizz Uganda: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

At [Blizz Uganda](http://www.ugblizz.com/), The privacy of our visitors is extremely important and is handled with care. Our Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used. This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy. 

### Log Files

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include: 

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP Adress)
  * Types of browser 
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp 
  * Referring and exit pages 
  * Number of clicks 

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.   
It is kept for our record and is deleted after the yearly visitors analysis is made.

###  Cookies 

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, All Blogging Tips has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.   
You may wish to turn off your cookies, you can do so from your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

### Other 

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from Blizz Uganda. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link. If you’ve any question about our privacy policy please Contact Us.

Last Updated 12 June 2015
